Guide to the Schickel family papers, 1905-1965
Schickel family papers, 1905-1965
- Series IV. Personal Papers
  - Schickel Family genealogy and Schickel Family memoirs, Date unknown (Box 20)